511 Germantown Ct. Warminster, PA 18974 Brandon.Stevens001@gmail.com

www.brandonrails.com

IT Specialist with over 3+ years of experience in electronic health records, information security and troubleshooting. Highly familiar with a fast pace, high pressure, dynamic work environment. Possess a Bachelor Degree in Corporate Communications and Business.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Operating systems: Windows 2000/Me/XP/7/8, Mac OS X, Unix, Linux

Software Applications: MS Office, Lotus Notes, Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Fireworks

Applications Continued: Salesforce, Microsoft SQL server 2008 **Languages:** SQL, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Ruby on Rails

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Nextgen Healthcare Horsham, PA

KBM Templates Analyst

July 2014 – Present

Used technical skill and acquired expertise of company's product to independently resolve issues, often times complex, with customer's database, software applications, technical configurations, etc.

- Recognized multiple times for excellent customer service in addition to exceeding quarterly goals
- Responded to all support issues in less than two hours by telephone and maintained average resolution time of less than two days which is well under the company average
- Exercised independent judgement to determine the appropriate course of action to be taken based on the analysis performed and all possible solutions

Xaxis Horsham, PA

Data Analyst

November 2013 – July 2014

Demonstrated the ability to read and write an array of programming languages including JavaScript, Python, and jQuery to ensure client's advertisements are properly implemented into the OAS platform

- Successfully use cloud based platforms such as Salesforce to organize, delegate and complete daily workflow
- Collaborated with Media Strategy and Business Development to leverage historical campaign data for inventory forecasting and media proposals
- Provided analysis of campaign metrics, and suggested improvements to drive success of campaign.

Clark Associates Inc Philadelphia, PA

Sales Representative

June 2013 – November 2013

Listened to and analyze the customer's issues, investigating the problems, and providing strategic solutions.

- Fostered a team oriented environment by maintaining a positive, professional attitude in all correspondence within high pressure situations.
- Providing friendly, efficient, and accurate solutions for customers with the goal of customer loyalty and increased business sales

EDUCATION

Pennsylvania State University

University Park, PA

Bachelor Degree in Corporate Communications and Business, December 2012

• GPA 3.32/4.0